{
"question": "九日",
"answer": "ここのか"
},
{
"question": "来る",
"answer": "くる"
},
{
"question": "後",
"answer": "あと"
},
{
"question": "会社",
"answer": "かいしゃ"
},
{
"question": "一人",
"answer": "ひとり"
},
{
"question": "二人",
"answer": "ふたり"
},
{
"question": "側",
"answer": "そば"
},
{
"question": "否",
"answer": "いいえ"
},
{
"question": "辛い",
"answer": "からい"
},
{
"question": "門",
"answer": "もん"
},
{
"question": "角-1",
"answer": "かど"
},
{
"question": "毎月",
"answer": "まいつき"
},
{
"question": "七",
"answer": "しち"
},
{
"question": "伯母さん",
"answer": "おばさん"
},
{
"question": "四",
"answer": "し"
},
{
"question": "お風呂",
"answer": "おふろ"
},
{
"question": "お酒",
"answer": "おさけ"
},
{
"question": "入口",
"answer": "いりぐち"
},
{
"question": "出口",
"answer": "でぐち"
},
{
"question": "お皿",
"answer": "おさら"
},
